Rehn Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, A-Z, 1858-1969, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-15; 14.4 linear feet; Reels 5849-5869)
  - Rahming - Randolph, 1940-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 268-332)
    Railway Express Agency
    Rains, Claude and Frances
    Rand, Nellie
    Randel, Mrs. L.
    Randolph, Frances
  - Randolph-Macon Woman's College, 1942-1964 (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 333-424)
  - Rannels - Rehn, Margaret Selby, 1903-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 425-511)
    Ranells, Neil J.
    Raphael, A.
    Rasko, Joseph
    Rattner, Ruth
    Rawson, Catherine G.
    Read, Helen Appleton
    Realty Management, Inc.
    Reasoner, David
    Record, Dorothy
    Redmond, Peter L.
    Reed, Adrienne
    Brooks Reed Gallery, Inc.
    Reed, Mark
    Reed, Walt
    Rees, Clarence E.
    Reese, H. P.
    Regan Bros.
    Regan, Frank A.
    Regency Hotel
    Regier, Harold M.
    Rehn, Frank L. (cousin)
    Rehn, Kitty
    Rehn, Margaret Selby (mother)
  - Rehn, Margarete, 1954-1968 (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 512-627)
  - Rehn, Peggy Wrenn - Rhodes, 1920-1945, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 628-727)
    Rehn, Peggy Wrenn (first wife)
    Reich, Sheldon
    C. J. Reid and Co., Inc.
    Reid, John C.
    Reiffel, Charles
    Reilly, Paul M.
    Henry Reinhardt and Son Galleries, Inc.
    Reisner, Mrs.
    Reiss, Jacob
    Renthal, Charles H.
    Resor, Mrs. Stanley
    Reubling, Agnes
    Reynal and Hitchcock, Inc.
    Reynolds, Mrs. Jackson
    Reynolds, L. M.
    Reynolds, Mrs. M. A.
    Rhana, Jim
    Rheinstein, Sidney
    Rhind, J. Massey
    Rhode Island School of Design and Museum of Art
    Rhodes, Mrs. Leland S.
  - De Ribcowsky - Riwchun, 1927-1966, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 728-828)
    De Ricowsky, D.
    Rich, Adelaide Steere
    Rich, Jack C.
    Rich, Mr. and Mrs. Walter H.
    Richards, Mary
    Richards, Meryl
    Richards, Ravland
    Richardson, Beverley
    Richmond Area University Center
    Rifocar
    Rifkin, Beatrice
    Riggs, Robert
    Rike-Kumler Co.
    Riley, Chapin and Mary Alexander
    Rindfoos, C. S.
    John and Mabel Ringling Museum of Art
    Rittler, Ralph L.
    River Dell Senior High School
    River Road Gallery
    Riverside Museum (See also Master Institute of United Arts, Inc.)
    Riwchun, Meyer H.
  - Robb - Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1924-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 829-951)
    Robb, W.
    Robbins, Raisa
    Roberson Memorial Center
    Roberts, Betty
    Roberts, C. Purcell
    Roberts, Elizabeth W.
    Roberts, Mrs. G. Brinton
    Roberts, Isaac W.
    Roberts, Ruth C.
    Robertson, Retta
    Robinett, William L.
    Robins, Louisa
    Robinson, Bernardine
    Robinson, Mrs. Chalfant
    Robinson, Edward G.
    Robinson, Ina
    Robinson, Mary Turlay
    Roby, Mrs. Joseph
    Sara Roby Foundation
    Roche, Robert
    Rochester Memorial Art Gallery
  - Rockefeller - Roosevelt, 1919-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 952-1023)
    Rockefeller, David
    Rockefeller, Mrs. John D., III
    Rockefeller, Nelson A.
    Rockland Foundation
    Rockland State Hospital
    Rogers, Mrs. Benjamin
    Rogers, Charles B.
    Rogers, Mrs. Francis
    Rogers, Mrs. Huddleston
    Rogers, Mrs. M.
    Rogers, William A.
    Rogers, Winifred W.
    Rogols, Barney B.
    Rohland, Paul
    Rohlf, J. A.
    Rohn, Florence W.
    Rohr, Norma Lee
    Rohrer, Warren
    Rolick, Esther G.
    Rolins College
    Rollo, Joe
    Roman, Herbert A.
    Rome, Mr. and Mrs. Morton E.
    Rook, Edward F.
    Rooney, Mrs. Alfred
    Roos, Alexander
    Roos, Beatrice Adams
    Roos, Mrs. C. P.
    Roos, Frank
    Roosevelt Field Art Center, Inc.
    Roosevelt, Franklin D. (about)
  - Root - Rosen, A., 1927-1957, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 1024-1099)
    Root, Edward W. and Grace
    Roren, Lydia
    Rosch, Mabel
    Rose, Billy
    Rosebrook, Jean F.
    Rosen, A.
  - Rosen, C. - Rozmus, Michael, Jr., 1924-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 1100-1202)
    Rosen, Charles and Jean
    Rosen, Samuel
    Rosenbloom, Charles J.
    Julius Rosenwald Fund
    Ann Ross Gallery
    Ross, Jane
    Ross, Sheldon
    Roth, Otto
    Rothman, Dr. and Mrs. Martin A.
    Rothman, Neville N., Jr. and Mary
    Rotunda Gallery (See City of Paris, Rotunda Gallery)
    Roupp, Helen C.
    Royal Art Framing
    Rozar, Morris
    Rozmus, Michael, Jr.
  - Rubenstein - Russo, 1924-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 1203-1286)
    Rubenstein, Lewis
    Rubin, J.
    Ruder and Finn Associates
    Rudick, Harry J. and Rose
    Rudin Management Co., Inc.
    Ruebling, Agnes
    Ruff, A. B.
    Rumsey, David
    Rush, Elizabeth
    Rush, H. Stockton
    Russell, Bols
    Russell, Marie L.
    Russell, Rosemary K.
    Russell, Sue Powers
    Russell, Mrs. Thomas C.
    Russell, Walter J.
    Russo, Alexander
  - Sacco - Samuels, 1926-1966, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 1288-1365)
    Sacco, Giovanni
    Saginaw Museum
    St. Alban's School
    St. Botolph Club
    Saint-Gaudens Memorial
    St. Louis Artists' Guild
    St. Paul Gallery and School of Art
    Salem College
    Salmagundi Club
    Salman, David M.
    Saltpeter, Harry
    Saltonstall, Elizabeth
    Saltonstall, Nathaniel
    Samson, Mr. and Mrs. Charles F.
    Samstag, Gordon
    Samuels, Ruth G.
  - San Diego Fine Arts Festival, Inc. - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1921-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 1366-1465)
    San Diego Fine Arts Festival, Inc.
    San Francisco Museum of Art
    San Joaquin Light and Power Corporation
    San Jose State College
    Sanborn, Nestor
    Sandberg, Gladys
    Birger Sandzen Memorial Gallery
    Sanger, Edwina C.
    Santa Barbara Museum of Art
  - Sappe - Saturday Evening Post, circa 1927-1967, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 1466-1563)
    Sappe, Anthony
    Sarachek Fine Arts
    Saretzky, Mrs. Gary D.
    Sargent, John Singer
    Sargood, Amy
    Sarkisian, Sarkis
    Sasowsky, Norman
    Saturday Evening Post
  - Sauder - Saunders, circa 1927-1967, undated (Box 11, Reel 5864, Frame 13-29)
    Sauder, I. Emanuel
    Sauer, Ted
    Sauers, John F.
    Saul, Maurice B.
    Saunders, Olivia
    Saunders, Silvia
  - Savage - Schnitzer, 1921-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5864, Frame 30-128)
    Savage, Dorothy
    Savage, Mabel
    Savage, Paul
    Savage, Mrs. Philip J.
    Saving Fund Society of Germantown
    Sawyer, Alice
    Sawyer, Mrs. Ansley
    Sawyer, Maureen
    Sawyer, Wells M.
    Scarborough, Elizabeth
    Schacht Lanfranchi, Inc. (See Lansha Studios)
    Shaefer, F. M.
    Shaeffer Galleries
    Schaffer, Estelle
    Schanck, George
    Schauffler, Robert McE.
    Scheer, Eli
    Scheerer, Mrs. H. F.
    Scheiber, Israel Ben
    Scheirich, Alma
    Scherman, Mrs. Harry
    Schimmel, David and Inez R.
    Schmidlapp, Mrs. Carl
    Schmidt, Frances
    Schmidt, Katherine
    Schnabel, Paul
    Schnackenberg, Henry
    Schneider, Jo Anne
    Schneiderman, I. Arthur and Lucile M.
    Seymour Schneiderman and Associates
    Schnitzer, Kurt
  - School Art League of New York City - Scripps College, 1921-1967, undated (Box 11, Reel 5864, Frame 129-232)
    School Art League of New York City
    School of the Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (See also Museum of Fine Arts, Boston)
    School of Visual Arts
    Schouten, Charles E.
    Schrag, Karl
    Schramm, Dorothy and James S.
    Schulte, Antoinette
    Henry Schultheis Co.
    Schulze, Paul
    Schumm, Henrietta M.
    Schwartz, Alan E.
    Schwartz, Eric
    Schwartz, Jeff
    Schwartz, Nancy
    Schwartz Galleries (Samuel Schwartz)
    Schweider, Arthur
    Schweitzer, M. R.
    Schweizer, Mrs. Ralph George
    Science Illustrated
    Scobey, H. C.
    Scollin, E. A.
    Scorah, William E.
    Scott and Fowles
    Scott, Earl
    Scott, Jonathan
    Scott, William E.
    Scribner, Mrs. Arthur
    Charles Scriber's Sons
    Scripps College
  - Seachrist - Seiff, 1925-1967, undated (Box 11, Reel 5864, Frame 233-368)
    Seachrist, Effie (See also Little Gallery in the Woods)
    Sears, Roebuck and Co. (Vincent Price Collection)
    Sears, S. M.
    Seattle Art Museum
    Security Storage Co.
    Segat, Albert and Minnie
    Seiberling, John F.
    Seiberling, John F., Jr.
    Seidman, Mrs. Frank E.
    Seiff, Arthur
  - Semans - Sexton, 1926-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5864, Frame 369-449)
    Semans, Mary
    Senf, Mary Morrissey
    Sepeshy, Zoltan
    Serpa, Edward F.
    Service Men's Committee
    Sesquicentennial International Exposition
    Charles Sessler, Bookseller
    Seventeen
    Sewell, William J.
    Sexton, John L.
  - Shand - Shaw, 1918-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5864, Frame 450-496)
    Shand, Robert G.
    Shannon, Mr. and Mrs. Ogden K.
    Shapiro, Daisy V.
    Shapiro, Hilda
    Shapiro, Morton
    Sharison, Saul S.
    Sharon Creative Arts
    Sharp and Dohme
    Sharpe, Mary Elizabeth
    Sharpe, Mrs. N.
    Sharpless, Ti-Grace
    Shaughnessy, Edward
    Shaw, F. H.
    Shaw, Mrs. George H.
    Shaw, Samuel T.
  - Sheafer, 1925-1959, undated (Box 11, Reel 5864, Frame 497-571)
    Sheafer, Francis W.
    Sheafer, Henry
    Sheafer, Lesley Green
  - Sheets - Shum, 1919-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5864, Frame 572-670)
    Sheets, Millard
    Shelden, Mrs. Allen
    Sheldon, Mrs. Joseph V.
    Sheldon, Roy
    Shell Union Oil Corp.
    Shepherd College
    Shepherd, George B.
    Shepherd, James G.
    Shepler, Dwight
    Shepperd, John and Jeanne Shoemaker
    Sheppart, Mark
    Sherman, E. B.
    Sherman, Frederic Fairchild
    Sherry Wine and Spirits Co., Inc.
    Shields, M.
    Shiell, Jerome A.
    Shipman, Frank R.
    Shipman, Louis Evan
    Shippee, Robert
    Shippen, Richard
    Shively, Paul
    Shore Studio Galleries
    Shorey, George H.
    Shorewood Publishers, Inc.
    Shortess, George K.
    Shubert, Irvine J.
    Shulman, Herman
    Shulman, Morris
    Shulof and Co., Inc.
    Shulof, Joseph
    Shum, Alden F.
  - Siden - Smith, Charles W., 1918-1968, undated (Box 12, Reel 5864, Frame 672-774)
    Siden, Franklin D.
    Siegle, Fred
    Sills and Co.
    Silvermine Guild of Artists, Inc.
    Simon, Charles
    Simon, Howard
    Simon, Mrs. Maron J.
    Simpson, Alex, Jr.
    Simpson, Mrs. Kelly
    Sims, A.
    Sisti Gallery
    Skelton, Mrs. Owen R.
    Skidelsky, Sibilla
    Skidmore College
    Skillman Express and Storage Co.
    Skinner, Joseph A.
    Sklenar, V. H.
    Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture
    Slater Memorial Museum
    Slatin, Yeffe Kimball (See Kimball, Yeffe V.)
    Slatkin, Burton
    Sloan, Mrs. B. B.
    Sloan Galleries of American Paintings (See Valparaiso University)
    Sloan, John F.
    Robert S. Sloan Gallery
    W and J Sloane
    Slocum, John J.
    Slosberg, Helen
    Slotnick, M.
    Slusser, Jean Paul
    Smeltzer, Ann
    Smillie, George H.
    Smilow-Thielle Corp.
    Smith, Benjamin Biggs
    Smith, Cecil
    Smith, Charles F.
    Smith, Charles W.
  - Smith College Museum of Art - Smith, William G., 1919-1967, undated (Box 12, Reel 5864, Frame 775-896)
    Smith College Museum of Art
    Smith, David L.
    Smith, Frances E. H.
    Smith, Francis Drexel
    George Walter Vincent Smith Art Museum
    Smith, Gertrude Rumsey
    Smith, H. A. Hammond
    Smith, Henry
    Smith, James MacGregor
    Smith, James U., Jr.
    Smith, Lloyd Pierce
    Smith, Louis Miller
    Mollie Smith Gallery
    Smith, R. Earl
    Smith, Mrs. Solwin
    Smith, Mrs. Sydney
    Smith, Mrs. W. H.
    Smith, Wallace H.
    Smith, William G., Jr.
  - Smithsonian Institution - Soby, 1918-1968, undated (Box 12, Reel 5864, Frame 897-974)
    Smithsonian Institution (includes United States National Museum and National Collection of Fine Arts)
    Smyth, Urquhart and Marckwald, Inc.
    Smythe, Elizabeth
    Snow, Charles M.
    Snow, Frederic W.
    Snow, Walter
    Snyder, Henry Hale
    Snyderman, Joy
    Soby, James T.
  - Social Security Board - Soyer, 1940-1968, undated (Box 12, Reel 5864, Frame 975-1074)
    Social Security Board
    Society of American Etchers, Inc.
    Society of Arts and Crafts
    Society of Designer-Craftsmen
    Society of Liberal Arts (See Joslyn Memorial)
    Society of the Four Arts
    Soler-Roig, J.
    Solomon, A. K.
    Solomon, Frank
    Sommers, Norman and Judith
    Sommers, Sheldon Charles
    Sosland, David N. and Rheta
    Sosland, Louis
    Sosland, Sanders
    South Bend Art Association
    South County Art Association
    Southern Christian Leadership Conference
    Southern Illinois University
    Southern Vermont Art Center
    Southern Vermont Artists, Inc.
    Southwest Texas State College
    Southwestern Art Association
    Soyer, Raphael
  - Spaeth, Eloise and Otto, 1940-1956 (Box 12, Reel 5864, Frame 1075-1157)
  - Sparhawk-Jones, Elizabeth, 1941-1967, (3 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5864, Frame 1158-1436)
  - Sparhawk-Jones, Elizabeth, cont., 1941-1967, (3 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 12-148)
  - Spaulding, John T., 1921-1943 (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 149-261)
  - Speicher, Eugene and Elsie, 1923-1962, (3 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 262-534)
  - Speier - Speyer, 1920-1968, undated (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 620-709)
    Speier, Robert W.
    Speigel, Mrs. M. J., Jr.
    Speight, Francis
    Speiser, Maurice J.
    Speizman, Sylvia
    Spencer, Girard L.
    Spencer, Robert
    Spencer, Thomas G.
    Speyer, Everett G.
  - Spiller - Springville High School Art Association, 1924-1968, undated (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 710-809)
    Spiller, Mortimer
    Spiro, Harry
    Spivack, S. S.
    Spook Farm Gallery
    Sprague, Mrs. Frank J.
    Spreckles, Mrs. Adolph
    Spreter, R. S.
    Sprinchorn, Carl
    Springfield Art Museum (Mo.)
    Springfield Museum of Fine Arts (Mass.)
    Springold, N. B.
    Springville High School Art Association
  - Spruance - State Fair of Texas, 1923-1960, undated (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 810-904)
    Spruance, Benton
    Squier, Charles E.
    Squier, Margery A.
    Stahl, David G.
    Stallforth, Frederico
    Stamford Museum and Nature Center
    Stark, Janet C.
    Starring, Mason D., III
    State College of Washington
    State Fair of Texas
  - State University College at Buffalo, 1963-1968 (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 535-619)
  - State University of Iowa - Steadman, 1924-1967, undated (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 905-987)
    State University of Iowa
    Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences
    Stathos, Bill
    Steadman, William E.
  - Stein - Strater, Charles G., 1924-1967, undated (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 988-1107)
    Stein, Charles F.
    Steinbomer, Harris B. and Julie
    Steinbomer, Henry
    Steine, David
    Steiner, Jacqueline
    Steinman, Shirley Watkins
    Steinmetz, Grace T.
    Stephens, Barry
    Stern Brothers
    Stern, Sheldon D.
    Sternberg, Margaret
    Sterns, Gladys
    Stevens, Mrs. Daniel
    Stevens, Farrington
    Stevens, John Calvin
    Stevens, Lawrence Tenney
    Stevens, M. S.
    Stillman, Helen
    Robert L. Stillson Co.
    Stimson, Candace
    Stimson, Willa
    Stocker, Edith
    Pauline Stone Gallery
    Storm King Art Center
    Story, Oscar P.
    Strater, Charles G.
  - Strater, Henry, 1927-1968, (2 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 1108-1409)
  - Strater, Michael Henry - Swinney, 1918-1968, undated (Box 12, Reel 5865, Frame 1410-1489)
    Strater, Michael Henry
    Straus, E. K.
    Straus, Gerhard D.
    Straus, John W.
    Straus, Robert D.
    Strickland, Ed
    Streitmann, George H.
    Stringham, Edwin John
    Stromsted, Astri
    Stuart, Beatrice
    Stuart Galleries
    Stuart, Kenneth
    Studio Publications
    Stucki, Margaret E.
    Sues, Bargara
    Sugarman, Mark
    Sulecki, Mrs. John
    Sullivan, S.
    Summit Art Association
    Sundberg, Alan
    Super Service Motor Freight Co.
    Sutphin, Samuel Reid
    Suter, Samuel
    Suttorn, Ruth H.
    Swedish American Line
    Sweeney, Thomas W.
    Sweet Briar College
    Swinney, Walter
  - Swope Art Gallery, 1941-1965 (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 12-104)
  - Sylvester - Taylor, 1923-1967, undated (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 105-196)
    Sylvester, Albert L. and Elizabeth
    Sylvia, Marshall
    Syracuse Museum of Fine Arts (See also Everson Museum of Art)
    Syracuse University
    System Magazine
    Taber, George H.
    Tagliabue, Charles
    Talbot, G. B.
    Talbott, Charles H.
    Talman, Bigelow, Whittmore, Ltd.
    Tangwell, Tor Ake
    Tannahill, Mary H.
    Tannahill, Robert H.
    Tannen, Robert
    Tarbuth Gallery
    Tarleton, Mrs. M. L.
    Tate and Hall, Inc.
    Taylor, Charles G.
    Taylor, Fay
    Kenneth Taylor Galleries
    Taylor, Leslie B.
    Taylor, Prentiss
  - Teater - Thomas, 1922-1968, undated (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 197-285)
    Teater, Patricia
    Teitelbaum, Edith
    Temple, Mrs. Alan
    Temple Beth El
    Temple Rodeph Sholom
    Templeton, Robert
    Templin, Walter W.
    Temstrom, M.
    Ten Eyck, Barent
    Tenney, Kathryn L.
    Tepper, Benjamin
    Terbill, Mrs. J. B.
    Terner, Jacob and Sandra W.
    Terrell, Allen R.
    Terry Art Institute
    Thaison, Mrs. A.
    Thal, Adrian
    Thayer, Gerald H.
    Theatre Magazine
    Thiele, Alice K.
    13 West Gallery
    Thom, Edgar R.
    Thomas, Mrs. Clifford
    Thomas, Grace D.
    Thomas, J.
  - Frederic B. Thomason, Inc., 1926-1968, (4 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 286-548)
  - Thompson - Toledo Blade, 1918-1966, undated (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 549-608)
    Thompson, E.
    Thompson, G. Albert
    Thompson, Mayanko
    Thompson, Milton S.
    Thompson, Payson
    Thorne, Mrs. S. B.
    Thorward, Clara
    Three Rivers Arts Festival
    Thuss, Louise B.
    Thut, Emil
    Tice and Lynch, Inc.
    Tiffany and Co.
    Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation
    Tilney, Mrs. Bedford
    Tilyo, Edward F. and Marie H.
    Time
    Timken, Mrs. W. R.
    Timmins, George
    Tims, H.
    Tinson, Julia C.
    Titelman, Frank M.
    Titelman, Richard
    Title Guarantee and Trust Co.
    Tobins, Jane Corli
    Todd, Arthur
    Toledo Blade
  - Toledo Museum of Art, 1918-1963, (2 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 609-810)
  - Tomkins - Tucker, 1919-1960, undated (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 811-994)
    Tomkins, C., Jr.
    Tompkins, Mr. and Mrs. Frederick
    Tompkins, Winslow
    Tomlin, Bradley Walker
    Tooker, George
    Toplis and Harding, Inc.
    Tornello, Robert L.
    Toth, Robert Bela
    Town and Country Gallery
    Town and Country Magazine
    Town Garage
    Townsend, J. I., Jr.
    Tracy, Bartlett
    Tracy, Spencer
    A. Traina and Co., Inc.
    John E. D. Trask, Inc.
    Trattler, Charles Stewart
    Travelers Insurance Co.
    Traver, George A.
    Travis and Parks
    Trebilcock, Paul
    Trentham, Eugene
    Trevor, Mrs. Horace B.
    Trinity College
    Trivigno, Pat
    Tucker, Allen
  - Tucker, Richard Derby, 1956-1968 (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 995-1135)
  - Tucker, Samuel A. - Underwood, 1918-1968, undated (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 1136-1242)
    Tucker, Samuel A.
    Tucker, William E., Jr.
    Tucson Art Center, Inc.
    Tudor Publishing Co.
    Tudor, Rosamund
    Tulp, Ellen
    Turnbeth, Mary
    Turnbull, Grace H.
    Turner, Helen M.
    Turpin, Charles S.
    Tuthill, William H.
    Tutle, Day
    Tuxedo Park School
    Tweed Gallery
    Tweed, Harrison
    Uhlmann, R. Hugh
    Ulmer, w. L.
    Underwood Corp.
    Underwood, Ethel T.
  - United Federation of Postal Clerks - United States War Production Board, 1919-1967, undated (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 1243-1334)
    United Federation of Postal Clerks
    United Fruit Co.
    United Hospital Fund of New York
    United Jewish Appeal
    United Modern Art in Boston
    United National Association of Post Office (Clerks') Craftsmen
    United Nations Children's Fund/UNICEF
    United Nations Tribute and International Festival of Arts
    United Republican Finance Committee
    United States Committee of the International Association of Plastic Arts
    United States Department of the Army
    United States Department of Justice
    United States Department of Labor
    United States Department of State
    United States Foreign Service
    United States House of Representatives, Ways and Means Committee
    United States National Museum (See Smithsonian Institution)
    United States Office of War Information
    United States Treasury Department
    United States War Department
    United States War Production Board
  - University Club - University of Georgia, 1941-1968, undated (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 1335-1428)
    University Club
    University of Arizona
    University of California, Los Angeles
    University of Georgia
  - University of Illinois - University of Kentucky, 1947-1968, undated (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 1429-1515)
    University of Illinois, Krannert Art Museum
    University of Kansas
    University of Kentucky
  - University of Maine - University of Montana, 1940-1967, undated (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 1516-1597)
    University of Maine
    University of Manitoba
    University of Maryland
    University of Miami, Joe and Emily Lowe Art Gallery
    University of Michigan
    University of Minnesota, Duluth
    University of Minnesota, Minneapolis
    University of Missouri
    University of Montana
  - University of Nebraska, 1940-1963 (Box 13, Reel 5867, Frame 12-133)
  - University of New Mexico - Vander Poel, 1922-1968, undated (Box 13, Reel 5867, Frame 134-231)
    University of New Mexico
    University of North Carolina
    University of Oklahoma
    University of Oregon
    University of Pennsylvania
    University of Pittsburgh
    University of South Carolina
    University of Southern California
    University of Texas
    University of Utah
    University of Vermont
    University of Virginia
    University of Washington
    University of Wisconsin, Elvehjm Art Center
    University of Wyoming
    University Press
    University Prints
    Upjohn Company
    Uplinger, Mrs. J. E.
    Upton, D. F.
    Urig, Russel
    Urquhart,Tony
    Usui, Bumpei
    Utica Public Library
    Utley, Gordon D.
    Vachon, Andrew William
    Vahinger, Fred
    Alfred Valente Gallery
    Valparaiso University, Sloan Galleries of American Paintings
    Van Buren, Jessica T.
    Van Evera, Caroline
    E. H. Van Ingen and Co.
    Van Pelt, Andrew
    Van Veen, S.
    Vander Poel, H. B.
  - Verle Gallery - Virges, 1920-1967, undated (Box 13, Reel 5867, Frame 232-292)
    Verle Gallery
    Verleger, F. Kind
    Vermont, Louise
    Vezin, Charles
    Vidor, King
    James Vigeveno Galleries
    Vincent, Fred C.
    Vincent, Harry A.
    Virges, E. M., II
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1939-1961 (Box 13, Reel 5867, Frame 293-434)
  - Vitale - Von Stein, 1924-1963, undated (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 436-453)
    Vitale, Ferruccio
    Vivino, Elmer
    Vogue
    Volz, Harry A.
    von Keller, Beatrice
    Von Stein, William G.
  - R. C. and N. A. Vose/Robert C. Vose Galleries, 1919-1967 (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 454-552)
  - Voth - Wade, 1924-1964, undated (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 553-560)
    Voth, Harold M.
    B. B. Wachtel Insurance
    Waddington Galleries, Inc.
    Wade, J. H.
  - Wadsworth Athenaeum, 1927-1965, undated (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 561-683)
  - Wadsworth, Isabella - Walden School, 1918-1968, undated (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 684-712)
    Wadsworth, Isabella
    Wager, Stella
    Wagman, Evelyn L.
    Wagner, Richard E.
    Wakefield-Young Books
    Walbridge, Norton S.
    Wald, J. S.
    Waldburger, Ernest R. S.
    Walden School
  - Walker Art Center, 1943-1967 (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 713-798)
  - Walker, Edith - Warner, Keith, 1919-1968, undated (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 799-905)
    Walker, Edith
    Walker Galleries/Maynard Walker/Collectors' Finds
    Walker, Harrington F.
    Walker, Mrs. Hudson D.
    Walker, Joseph
    Walker, Maynard (See Walker Galleries)
    Walker, Robert N.
    Walker, Stewart
    Walker, Wes